该死的walletnook.com!
Damn you,walletnook.Com!
有什么问题吗?
Problem?
网站上的产品说明 完全是在误导
The online description was completely misleading.
上面说 有八个插缝 加一个可抽取的ID卡夹
They said eight slots,plus removable id.
对任何理性人来说 那意味着可以放九张卡
To any rational person,that would mean room for nine cards,
但上面没告诉你 可抽取的ID卡夹也占了一个插缝
but they don't tell you,the removable id takes up one slot.
简直是恶梦!
It's a nightmare!
好吧 你真的需要那张
Okay,now,do you really need
美国荣誉审判联盟的会员卡吗?
the honorary justice league of america membership card?
从5岁起就一直 存放在我的钱包里
It's been in every wallet I've owned since I was five.
为什么?
Why?
它上面写着"请随时随身携持本证"
It says "keep this on your person at all times."
就在蝙蝠侠签名的下面
it's right here under batman's signature.
…这就是莱纳德和谢尔顿的房间
…And this is leonard and sheldon's apartment.
猜猜谁的父母刚装了宽带
Guess whose parents just got broadband.
莱纳德 容我介绍 新德里现场连线
Leonard,may I present,live from new delhi,
V.M.库萨帕里医生及夫人
Dr.And mrs.V.M.Koothrappali.
你们好!
Hi!
把摄像头抬起来! 我正在看他的裤裆
Tilt up the camera up! I'm looking at his crotch.
抱歉 爸爸
Sorry,papa.
噢 好多了
Oh,that's much better.
- 嗨! - 嗨!
- Hi. - Hi!
这边的是谢尔顿
And over here is sheldon.
嗨!
Hi!
他和莱纳德住一起
He lives with leonard.
噢 真不错
Oh,that's nice.
就像哈罗恩和塔维尔一样
Like haroon and tanvir.
不 不 跟哈罗恩和塔维尔不一样
No,no. Not like haroon and tanvir.
多么可爱的年轻人啊
Such sweet young men.
他们刚刚收养了一个很可爱的小印度男孩
They just adopted the cutest little punjabi baby.
不是 我们跟哈罗恩和塔维尔不一样
No,we're not like haroon and tanvir.
你们和我儿子一样 是搞研究的?
So,are you boys academics like our son?
是的
Yes.
你们父母对你们那点可怜收入也无所谓吗?
And your parents are comfortable with your limited earning potential?
- 哦 是的 - 完全不
- Oh,yes. - Not at all.
爸爸 拜托 不要再提这些了
Papa,please. Don't start.
只是随便问问
It was just a question.
他太敏感了
He's so sensitive.
好啦 这就是我的生活 他们是我的朋友
Okay,that's my life. That's my friends.
很高兴见到你们 说再见
Good to see you. Say good-bye.
- 再见 - 再见
- Bye. - Bye.
等一下!
Wait! Wait!
你关之前 我们还有个好消息要告诉你
Before you go,we have good news.
把电脑放下 把你朋友们聚过来
Put the computer down and gather your friends.
- 什么 爸爸? - 我没看到你朋友
- What is it,papa? -I don't see your friends.
你们不觉得网上聊天
Is it just me,or does web chatting
穿着衣服很无聊吗?
with your clothes on seem a little pointless?
拉杰 你还记得拉丽塔・古塔吗?
Rajesh,do you remember lalita gupta?
那个用萨摩萨饼打我 还叫我贱民的小肥妞?
The little fat girl that used to kick me in the samosas and call me untouchable?
是的
Yes.
她现在在南加州大学 学牙科专业
Well,now she's a dental student at usc,
我们把你的联系方式给了她
so we gave her your contact information.
你们干嘛那么做?
Why did you do that?
你已经26岁了 拉杰
You're 26 years old,rajesh.
我们想抱孙子
We want grandchildren.
可是爸爸 我不想...
But,papa,I'm not supposed...
拉丽塔的父母同意了你们的婚事
lalita's parents approved the match.
如果你决定春天举办婚礼 还可以避开雨季
If you decide on a spring wedding,we can avoid monsoon season.
春天就结婚?
A spring wedding?
你自己决定 孩子
It's up to you,dear.
我们可不想干涉
We don't want to meddle.
既然你们不想干涉 干嘛要干涉我的事?
If you don't want to meddle,then why are you meddling?
我说一句 你父母可能不认为这是干涉
If I may,your parents probably don't consider this meddling.
包办婚姻如今虽已不常见
While arranged marriages are no longer the norm,
但印度父母仍然在他们子女的婚姻中
indian parents continue to have
扮演着比以往更重要的角色
a greater-than-average involvement in their children's love lives.
为什么我们自己文化还要你来教导?
Why are you telling me about my own culture?
你看起来很困惑
You seemed confused.
抱歉 妈妈 爸爸 尽管我非常尊重你们
Sorry,mumi,papa,but with all due respect,
- 但我真的不想... - 对不起 孩子
- I really don't want to... - I'm sorry,darling.
我们不能再聊了
We have to go.
1989-1993年的美国电视剧
开始了
Doogie howser is on.
奶奶 时间到了!
Grandma! It's doogie time!
- 拜拜! - 拜拜!
- Bye-bye! - Bye-bye!
真不敢相信
I don't believe it.
我也是
Neither do I.
快20年没播了
Doogie howser's been off the air for like 20 years.
其实我读到过 它在印度是最受欢迎的电视节目
Actually,I read somewhere that it's one of the most popular programs in india.
我认为希望有个当医生的孩子
It might speak to a cultural aspiration
可能是种文化向往吧
to have one's children enter the medical profession.
说的没错
I bet you're right.
我猜他们喜欢看
I bet they love scrubs.
有不喜欢的吗?
What's not to love?
喂! 在听吗?
Excuse me! Hello?
我父母想要我娶一个 根本不认识的人
My parents are trying to marry me off to a total stranger.
我该怎么办?
What am I going to do?
我建议你坦然接受吧
I suggest you go through with it.
什么?
What?
建立在浪漫爱情上的婚姻
Romantic love as the basis for marriage
只是从19世纪开始盛行
has only existed since the 19th century.
在那之前都是包办婚姻
Up until then,arranged marriages were the norm,
也很好地适应了社会发展
and it served society quite well.
1964年著名的百老汇长篇音乐剧
那正是的蓝本
It's the entire premise of fiddler on the roof.
我不是音乐剧的粉丝 但我超爱那部音乐剧
I'm not a big fan of musicals,but I love that show.
我也是
Me too.
当然 对我来说很有文化感染力
Of course,it speaks to me culturally.
可以理解 但这类故事一般都超越了种族
Understandable,but there's a universality to that story which transcends ethnicity.
让人没法忘记里面那些 琅琅上口的曲调
Let's not forget it's got some really catchy tunes.
- 噢 的确 - 就是啊!
- oh,absolutely. - Yeah!
好吧 我知道该怎么做了
Okay,I know what I'm going to do.
什么?
What?
去找新朋友
Find new friends.
那谁去租那部音乐剧?
so who wants to rent fiddler?
没必要 我们有特别收藏版
No need,we have the special edition.
也许我们真的就像哈罗恩和塔维尔
Well,maybe we are like haroon and tanvir.
《生活大爆炸》
第一季  第08集
The.Grasshopper.Experiment
我是谢尔顿 ・库珀博士
this is dr.Sheldon cooper.
我想取消天文馆的会员资格
Yeah,I need to cancel my membership to the planetarium.
我也很抱歉 但我钱包里没地方放你们的会员卡了
Well,I'm sorry,too,but there's just no room for you in my wallet.
我能理解 但我要在 你们和自然历史博物馆中选择
I understand,but it was between you and the museum of natural history,
坦白说 你们那儿可没有恐龙
and frankly,you don't have dinosaurs.
我也会想你的 再见
I'll miss you,too. Bye-bye.
好啦 我知道你们在发短信宣扬我的事 你们最好停下来
Okay,I know you're texting about me and I'd really like you to stop.
天呐 我彻底完蛋了
oh,dear,I am rightly and truly screwed.
嗨 我以为你去找新朋友了
Hey,I thought you were finding new friends.
我是有伸出触角(尝试过)
I've got some feelers out.
在此同时 听听这个
In the meantime,listen to this.
嗨 拉杰 我是拉丽塔・古塔
Hi,rajesh. This is lalita gupta.
我妈把你的电话号码转交给我
Uh,your mother gave my mother your phone number to give to me.
所以我打给你 …回我电话 拜
So,I'm calling you and… call me back. Bye.
你们能相信吗 她居然逼得那么紧
Can you believe how pushy she is?
那就别回她电话
So don't call her.
如果不打给她 我就再也别想和我父母说话了
If I don't call her,I won't hear the end of it from my parents.
那就打给她
So call her.
我怎么打给她? 你知道我不能和女人说话
How can I call her? You know I can't talk to women.
我没辙了 其他人呢?
I'm done. Anybody else?
- 电话给我 - 干嘛?
- Give me the phone. - Why?
只管给我好了
Just give it to me.
你做什么?
What are you doing?
别担心 你会感激我的
Don't worry. You'll thank me.
喂 拉丽塔? 我是拉杰・库萨帕里
Hello,lalita?Raj koothrappali here.
是的 我也很高兴和你说话
Yes,it is good to talk to you,too.
你现在穿的什么?
So what are you wearing?
噢 那不重要
Oh,not important.
总之 你想什么时候见面?
Uh,so,anyhow,when would you like to meet?
周五没问题
Friday works for me!
具体时间地点 我再打给你
I'll call you with a time and place.
还有 我是认真的 宝贝
But in the meantime,keep it real,babe.
现在你可以感激我了
You may now thank me.
谢什么? 把我的声音弄得像 辛普森一家似的?
For what? Making me sound like a simpsons character?
那好吧 下次你自己去约她
Fine. Next time make your own date.
这次我都不想!
I didn't want to make this one!
往好的方面想吧 也许她已经是个美丽动人的姑娘呢
Look on the bright side,she might turn out to be a nice,beautiful girl.
好极了 那我们就会结婚
Great,then we'll get married,
但我一句话都没办法跟她说
I won't be able to talk to her
我们一起的余生就会沉默中度过
and we'll spend the rest of our lives in total silence.
我父母就是这样
It worked for my parents.
- 嗨 伙计们 - 嗨
- hi,guys. - Oh,hey.
我需要几只"豚鼠"做实验
I need some guinea pigs.
在洛杉矶瑞赛达有家供应实验动物的公司 你可以去试试
Okay,there's a lab animal supply company in reseda you could try.
但如果你的研究需要人类志愿者
But if your research is going to have human applications,
我能建议你换成小白鼠吗?
may I suggest white mice instead?
它们大脑的机能和人类的更接近
Their brain chemistry is far closer to ours.
我向上帝发誓 谢尔顿 总有一天
I swear to god,sheldon,one day,
我会跟上你的说话思维
I'm going to get the hang of talking to you.
这话他妈妈说了好多年了
His mom's been saying that for years.
什么事?
What's up?
好吧 我总算说服餐馆老板 把我换到吧台
Well,I finally convinced the restaurant to give me a bartending shift,
所以我需要练习调酒
so I need to practice mixing drinks.
哦 太好了
Oh,great.
任何事情的成功关键 都是熟能生巧
Well,the key to acquiring proficiency in any task is repetition.
显然也有例外
With certain obvious exceptions.
比如说 自杀
Suicide,for example.
莱纳德 怎么样?
So,leonard,how about it?
你知道 佩妮 我们很乐意帮助你
You know,penny,we'd love to help you,
但拉杰现在正遇到了点麻烦
but 拉杰 is going through some stuff right now,
而且他不喝酒 所以...
and besides,he doesn't drink,so...
是吗?
really?
拉杰现在很痛苦 所以愿意尝试喝酒
Um,raj is going through some stuff right now and he'd like to take up drinking.
好了 给你 莱纳德
Okay,here you go,leonard.
龙舌兰日出酒
One tequila sunrise.
谢谢
Thank you.
知道吗 这杯酒能极好地诠释
You know,this drink is a wonderful example of
在各自不同重力下
how liquids with different specific gravities
液体是如何在圆柱容器内相互作用的
interact in a cylindrical container.
谢谢
Thank you.
好吧 拉杰 你要什么?
Okay,raj,what'll it be?
随便你推荐
Whatever you recommend.
草蜢酒怎么样?
Uh,how about a grasshopper?
草蜢酒我很在行
I make a mean grasshopper.
行吗? 好的
Okay? Good.Coming up.
谢尔顿 你要什么?
Sheldon,what are you going to have?
我要一杯无糖可乐
I'll have a diet coke.
好吧 你能点鸡尾酒吗?
Okay,can you please order a cocktail?
我需要练习调酒
I need to practice mixing drinks.
好吧
Fine.
我要圣洁古巴利布瑞酒
I'll have a virgin cuba libre.
那是朗姆可乐酒 去掉朗姆酒
That's,um,rum and coke without the rum.
对
Yes.
- 那么...可乐 - 是的
- So...coke. - Yes.
能调制成无糖的吗?
And would you make it diet?
冰箱里有罐装的
There's a can in the fridge.
古巴利布瑞酒通常是用高脚杯盛放 并且杯口放上酸橙
A cuba libre traditionally comes in a tall glass with a lime wedge.
那你游去古巴吧
Then swim to cuba.
吧台侍者应该热情待人才对
Bartenders are supposed to have people skills.
好啦
Okay.
拉杰 给你
Raj,here you go.
好啦 下一个到谁?
All right. Who's next?
我想试试 光滑的咪咪
I'd like to try a slippery nipple.
好吧 跳过你了
Okay,you're cut off.
谁要续杯?
Anybody need a refill?
我的人生驶向何方 佩妮?
Where did my life go,penny?
眼下我还是无忧无虑的单身汉
One day I'm a carefree bachelor,
转眼我就结婚了 载着一车小孩
and the next I'm married and driving a minivan
去新德里郊区打板球
to peewee cricket matches in suburban new delhi.
你在跟我说话?
Are you talking to me?
这儿还有别人叫佩妮?
Is there another penny here?
我有计划
I had such plans.
我有梦想
I had dreams.
我要成为粒子天体物理学界的甘地
I was going to be the indira gandhi of particle astrophysics.
当然是有小鸡鸡的
But with a penis,of course.
太神了
Amazing.
我还小的时候
Ever since I was a little boy,
我爸就想让我像他一样当妇科医生
my father wanted me to be a gynecologist like him.
我哪能做妇科医生?
How can I be a gynecologist?
我都不敢看女人的眼睛!
I can barely look a woman in the eye!
知道吗?
You know what?
我再也不要父母控制我的人生了
I'm not going to let my parents control my future any longer.
是时候摊牌了
It's time for a showdown.
谁给我一个带摄像头的电脑!
Somebody give me a computer with a webcam!
亲爱的 我觉得这是酒劲儿的作用
Okay,sweetie,I think that's the grasshopper talking.
我要告诉我父母
And it's about to tell my parents that
我绝不会跟拉丽塔・古塔 骑象走向圣坛（结婚）
I'm not riding an elephant down the aisle with lalita gupta.
好啦 冷静
Okay,calm down.
没人能逼你结婚
Look,no one can make you get married.
不如跟她见见面 看会怎么样?
Why don't you just meet this girl and see what happens?
你没听我说吗?
Haven't you been listening to me?
我不能跟女人说话
I cannot talk to women.
呃 拉杰
Um,raj...
别说 看他多久才醒悟
no,no,let's see how long it takes him.
拉杰 亲爱的 你说你不能跟女人说话
Um,raj,honey,you say you can't talk to women,
可你一直在跟我说话
but you've been talking to me.
这将是个永远的谜
And now we'll never know.
说的对...
You're right. I...
我正在和你说话
I am talking to you.
你好 佩妮 怎么样?
Hello,penny,how are you?
我很好
I'm fine.
现在我只需确保 和草蜢酒见面之前 先喝一杯拉丽塔
Okay,now I just need to make sure I have a lalita before I meet the grasshopper.
真是甜蜜的绿色奇迹
It's a sweet,green miracle.
好吧 如果你要靠酒撑过这次约会
Okay,if you're going to drink on this date,
答应我不要太过头
just promise me you won't overdo it.
什么过头?
Overdo what?
快乐过头?
Happiness?
自由过头?
Freedom?
能保证我一切都将顺利无比的 这股体内热流?
This warm glow inside of me that promises everything's going to be all hunky-dunky?
没错
Yeah,that.
你带她来我的餐馆吧
Why don't you bring her to my restaurant
我在吧台可以照看你们
while I'm tending the bar so I can keep an eye on you.
好
Okay.
等等 你们什么计划?
Wait a minute. What's the plan here?
让他俩见面 他喜欢她 娶她
Let's say he meets her,he likes her,they get married.
然后在酒精的麻痹下度过余生?
What's he going to do,stay drunk for the rest of his life?
我父母就是这样
Worked for my parents.
不敢相信小拉丽塔・古塔就坐在我旁边
I can't believe I'm sitting here next to little lalita gupta.
事实如此了
Well,you are.
小拉丽塔
Little lalita.
说起来很好玩
That's fd of kinun to say.
小拉丽塔 小拉丽塔 小拉丽塔
Little lalita,little lalita,little lalita.
你可以试试
You should try it.
不用了
Oh,it's okay.
你瘦了好多啊
You have lost so much weight.
肯定吃了不少苦头吧 因为你以前好胖好胖
That must have been difficult for you because you were so,so fat.
你还记得吗?
Do you remember?
我记得
Yes,I do.
当然记得了
Of course you do.
肥成那样 谁能忘得了?
Who could forget being that fat?
我一直在努力忘记
Well,I've been trying.
你现在学牙科了
So you're a dental student.
你知道吗? 牙医的自杀率特别高
Mm,are you aware that dentists have an extremely high suicide rate?
当然没有空中交通管制员高
Not as high as,say,air traffic controllers,but,then,
但是牙医要比空中交通管制员多很多
there are far mo dreentists than air traffic controllers,
所以单就数量来说 还是你们胜出
so in pure numbers,you're still winning.
是啊!
Yay,me.
你有没有什么酒能让他轻点闹腾?
Do you have a drink that will make him less obnoxious?
酒是没有这种功能的
Drinks do not work that way.
我觉得他没问题 看她
I'd say he's doing fine. Look at her.
上次我妈给我找的女孩 是个留着胡子的秃子
The last girl my mom set me up with had a mustache and a vestigial tail.
对不起 我来晚了
Sorry I'm late.
怎么了?
What happened?
没什么 我就是有点不太想来
Nothing. I just really didn't want to come.
请来一杯"圣洁无糖古巴利布瑞酒"
Virgin diet cuba libre,please.
好吧
Okay.
用高脚杯 要插柠檬片
In a tall glass with a lime wedge.
我这就插
Oh,I'll wedge it right in there.
库萨帕里怎么样…
So how's koothrappali...
噢 我的天
oh,my lord.
什么?
What?
这是潘查理公主
That's princess panchali.
我很确定她叫拉丽塔
I'm pretty sure her name's lalita.
不是 是里的潘查理公主
No,no,princess panchali,from the monkey and the princess.
哦 对
Oh,yeah.
我想在网上看来着 不过要信用卡的
I tried to watch that online,but they wanted my credit card.
那是儿童故事
It's a children's story.
不 它不是
Oh,no,it isn't.
我小时候有一次生了病
When I was a little boy and got sick,
我经常生病 我妈妈会读这个故事给我听
which was most of the time,my mother would read it to me.
讲述一只与众不同而遭同类取笑的猴子
It's about an indian princess who befriends a monkey
后来和印度公主成为好朋友的故事
who was mocked by all the other monkeys because he was different.
因为某些原因 它引起我的强烈的共鸣
For some reason,I related to it quite strongly.
我知道原因
I know the reason.
我们都知道
We all know the reason.
谢尔顿 你想说什么?
Sheldon,what are you getting at?
那个女人像极了书上的潘查理li公主
That woman looks exactly like the pictures of princess panchali in the book.
多难得见到一个你喜欢的角色 活生生在眼前啊
How often does one see a beloved fictional character come to life?
每年动漫展上
Every year at comic-con.
迪斯尼每天都有
Every day at disneyland.
你都可以把白雪公主雇到家里
You can hire snow white to come to your house.
当然 最好是家里有小孩
Of course,they prefer it if you have a kid.
伙计们
Hey,guys.
她是拉丽塔・古塔
Isth is lalita gupta.
拉丽塔 这是莱纳德 谢尔顿 霍华德 还有佩妮
Lalita,this is leonard and sheldon and howard and penny.
你们说多好? 她不是肥女了
Isn't it great? She isn't fat anymore.
请原谅 公主陛下 我只是一只猴子
Forgive me,your highness,for I am but a monkey,
我的天性就是爬树
and it is in my nature to climb
我不是故意在你梳头时弄乱你的头发
I did not mean to gaze upon you as you comb your hair.
你说什么?
I'm sorry?
你简直是美貌的潘查理公主的真身啊
You are the living embodiment of the beautiful princess panchali.
不要开玩笑了
Oh,no kidding.
那人是谁i?
Who... who is that?
我最爱的印度童话主角
A beloved character from an indian folktale.
是我们这样的印度人 还是开赌场的印第安?
Us indian or "come to our casino" indian?
你们这样的
You indian.
简直太像了
The resemblance is remarkable.
我简直可以闻到你黑发上 点缀的荷花香
I can practically smell the lotus blossoms woven into your ebony hair.
谢谢
Well,thanks.
我想你的味道一定也很好
I imagine you smell very nice,too.
我每天洗两次澡 洗手无数次
I shower twice a day and wash my hands as often as I can.
真的? 我也是
Really? So do I.
但你是牙科学生 他只是疯子
But you're a dentist. He's nuts.
不要骂人 拉杰
Don't be insulting,rajesh.
谢尔顿 跟我说说那个跟我长得很像的公主吧
So,sheldon,tell me more about this princess you say I look like.
传说 她的眼睛是神用星星做的
It was said that the gods fashioned her eyes out of the stars
她艳红的唇 令玫瑰都羞于开放
and that roses were ashamed to bloom in the presence of her ruby lips.
我的天
Oh,my.
滚开 谢尔顿
Back off,sheldon.
为什么?
What?
如果你再调戏我的女人
If you do not stop hitting on my lady,
你会感受到我炽热的怒火
you will feel the full extent of my wrath.
我没调戏她
I'm not hitting on her.
我也不是你的女人
And I am not your lady.
而且你也没有怒火
And you have no wrath.
你是我的女人
You are my lady.
我爸妈说了的
Our parents said so.
从各方面来说 我们都是百分之一百在一起了
We are,for all intents and purposes,100% hooked up.
好吧 有些话我跟你说清楚
Okay,let's get something straight here.
我今天来见你完全是敷衍我父母
The only reason I came tonight was to get my parents off my case.
我才不会嫁你这种老土人呢
I certainly don't need to be getting this old world crap from you.
潘查理公主就是凭这种精神
That's exactly the kind of spirit with which princess panchali
带领猴子走向自由
led the monkeys to freedom.
去他妈潘查理公主
Screw princess panchali.
不许你这么说我
Hey,you can't talk to me like that.
可你不是什么潘查理公主啊
But you're not princess panchali.
算你走运 否则她都能把你的头砍下来
Luckily for you-- she could have you beheaded.
谢尔顿 你饿吗?
Sheldon,are you hungry?
我想吃点东西
I could eat.
我们走
Let's go.
刚才怎么回事?
What just happened?
我也无法解释
Beats the hell out of me.
我告诉你怎么回事
I'll tell you what happened.
我想我学会怎么泡印度妞了
I just learned how to pick up indian chicks.
让我怎么跟拉丽塔的父母交待?
What are we supposed to say to lalita's parents?
我和她爸爸一起打高尔夫
I play golf with her father.
我都没法面对他了
I won't be able to look at him.
也许你应该看着球 爸爸
Maybe you should keep your eye on the ball,papa.
你现在懂搞笑了
Oh,now you're a funny man.
这不好笑! 搞笑先生
This is not funny,mr.Funny man.
库萨帕里医生及夫人 说句公道话
Dr.And mrs.Koothrappali,in all fairness,
也不全是拉杰的错
it wasn't entirely raj's fault.
这我们的家事 谢尔顿
This is a family matter,sheldon.
我是莱纳德
I'm leonard.
不好意思 你们老外全都一个样
Oh,sorry. You all look alike to us.
他说的对 爸爸
But he's right,papa.
听他的
Listen to him.
你! 你把一切事情都搞砸了
You! You are the one who ruined everything.
是谁? 我们看不见
Who is it? We can't see.
转过去 转过去
Turn us. Turn us.
说吧 告诉我父母 为什么他们抱不上孙子
Go ahead,tell my parents why they won't have any grandchildren.
我怎么知道?
How would I know?
你精子量不足?
Do you have a low sperm count?
跟我的精子量完全没关系
This has nothing to do with my sperm count.
我们寄给你的四角裤你穿着吧 拉杰?
You are wearing the boxers that we sent you,aren't you,rajesh?
穿着呢 妈妈
Yes,mumi.
穿那种紧身三角裤对小鸡鸡不好
Because you know what happens to the samosas when you wear tighty-whities.
能不能别提我的睾丸?
Can we please stop talking about my testicles?
谢尔顿 告诉他们你做了什么
Sheldon,tell them what you did.
我做了什么?
What did I do?
你抢走了他的约会对象
You left with his date.
朋友之间不能这样
Friends don't do that to each other.
好吧 知道了
All right,noted.
对不起
Sorry.
对不起? 你就说一个对不起完事?
Sorry? That's all you can say is sorry?
接受吧 拉杰 我连一句对不起都没收到过
Take it,raj. It's more than I've ever gotten.
我能否指出 她本来不会跟我走
And may I point out,she woavdn't hule asked me to go with her
如果你不是喝醉了又说一些令人讨厌的话
if you hadn't been drunk and boring.
喝醉?
Drunk?
还有令人讨厌 她的原话
And boring-- her words.
我就知道!
I knew it.
他去了美国 变成酒鬼了
He moves to america and he becomes an alcoholic.
我不是酒鬼
I'm not an alcoholic.
那你为什么喝醉?
Then why were you drunk?
就这一次 我发誓 爸爸
It was just this one time,papa,I swear.
你还否认？
Are you in denial?
要不要我们亲自去教育教育你?
Do we have to come over and do an intervention?
别让他在朋友面前丢脸
Don't embarrass him in front of his friends.
好吧
All right.
带我们出去
Carry us outside.
我们要私下谈
We want to talk to you in private.
- 爸爸 别... - 马上 拉杰!
- But,papa,please... - now,rajesh!
我要走了
I have to go.
你给我听好...
Now,listen to me...
至少等我到了走廊再说
at least wait till I get into the hall.
好吧 晚安
okay,well,good night.
等等
Hold on.
你和拉丽塔怎么样?
What happened with you and lalita?
我们吃饭 她告诉我牙周病和心脏病有关
We ate,she lectured me on the link between gum disease and heart attacks--
都是我早就知道的东西 然后我回家
nothing I didn't already know-- and I came home.
那你以后不会再去见她了？
So you're not going to see her again?
为什么要和她再见面?
Why would I see her again?
我已经有牙医了
I already have a dentist.
谁来告诉他的父母 永远都抱不上孙子了?
I wonder who's going to tell his parents they're not having grandchildren?
敬生命 敬生命 我致敬 *
To life,to life,l'chaim
我致敬 我致敬 敬生命 *
l'chaim,l'chaim,to life
生活给我们欢笑 有福有祸 干杯 *
life has a way of amusing us blessing and bruising us drink,
我致敬 敬生~命 *
l'chaim,to li...fe.
不敢相信 他中了什么邪?
I don't believe it. What's gotten into him?
也许一点圣洁古巴利布瑞酒 让他变得放浪了
maybe a couple virgin cuba libres that turned out to be kind of slutty.
你不是吧
You didn'T.
你们做你们的实验 我做我的
Hey,you do your experiments. I do mine.